It's raining on and off.
Right.
(It's pouring down, breaking through the summer heat.)
A subtropical climate?
I guess it's turning into that.
So we were supposed to film outdoors today.
The staff set everything up.
- It's pouring down.
- We had to pivot abruptly.
That's why we're filming inside a cafe.
But as soon as we started filming,
it stopped raining.
- Right.
- Look.
(It was pouring down like this earlier.)
This is one of those toughest days.
- Right. But it'd start raining...
- Yes.
- once we step out.
- Right.
We're in Gwangjin-gu. Right?
I used to live in Gwangjin-gu.
- Really?
- Yes.
I see. When?
When I was attending Sejong University.
(It's located in Gunja-dong, Gwangjin-gu.)
Listen.
- I understand...
- Well...
- that you love your alma mater.
- No, listen.
He's always mentioning the university.
Seriously. The university ought to give him an award.
The university is pleased with it.
So they told me a bit about today's guests.
- I didn't know about the guests.
- Okay.
But my stylist told me about them.
- So you heard?
- Yes.
Their stylist picked up an outfit that was set aside for our show.
I see. The stylists...
- went to pick up the outfits.
- Yes, it was during the pick-up.
My stylist glanced over...
and saw someone pick up the outfit that was set aside for our show.
My stylist saw the name too.
I didn't try to find out, but I ended up finding out anyway.
She was in "Teach You a Lesson."
- I really liked that drama.
- My gosh.
- Jin Ki Joo.
- It's Ki Joo.
Yes. I really enjoyed watching her drama.
Wait. Is she coming now?
Is she? Who's that? Ki Joo is coming?
So have you guys made a lot of headway with the filming?
Yes. We made a lot of headway with it.
And the director tends to shoot the scenes quite fast.
That's amazing.
I think it's Ki Joo.
One of them is Ki Joo.
But who's the other one?
My gosh.
Isn't that Cha Tae Hyun?
- I think it's Tae Hyun.
- It's Cha Tae Hyun again.
- Come on.
- Tae Hyun.
He's joining us again.
It's Tae Hyun again.
(Chuckling)
- CEO Cha.
- My gosh.
- Ki Joo.
- Hello.
- I brought her to round things out.
- Hello, Ki Joo.
- I see.
- Okay.
(He's been on the show for every season!)
(Every time he came on, they made it to Round 3,)
(and he always boosted the ratings.)
(The show's loving Whenever Friend, Cha Tae Hyun)
(She shot to national fame... with her role...)
(in a weekend drama, "Homemade Love Story.")
(She pulled off her characters in romantic comedies...)
(and nailed the action scenes to perfection.)
(The fully versatile actress, Jin Ki Joo)
(The 1st actress at CEO Cha's agency)
- Hello.
- I brought her too.
- Tae Hyun's agency...
- signed Ki Joo.
- That's right.
- Ki Joo.
- I know.
- How did you end up at his agency?
- You...
You brought an actress to our show.
- I'm here as her manager.
- I mean...
- My gosh.
- All right. Let's sit down.
- Sit there, Ki Joo.
- Tae Hyun is here again.
- By the way, - Yes.
Ki Joo joined the agency Tae Hyun and In Sung are running.
That's right.
- She signed with their agency.
- I mean... Yes.
Her drama, "Teach You a Lesson," was a huge hit.
- Right.
- Actually...
- You know what?
- It happened...
- I...
- right after you signed her.
I'm such a lucky guy.
Will I stay lucky until I die?
- How could this happen?
- Tae Hyun, you're such a lucky guy.
- Seriously.
- I agree.
It seems he's luckier than he is hardworking.
- Seriously.
- I mean it.
On top of that, when Bo Pil invited me to the show,
he said I was like the show's lucky charm.
It's my first time joining a show...
as its lucky charm.
So I'm practically the pig's head for this show.
That's how it feels.
- You're right.
- I guess it's like a ritual.
- It was so funny.
- Tae Hyun...
has to join us every season.
- He helps our season succeed.
- Yes.
- But the timing was great.
- Okay.
It's crazy. I'm so lucky.
(Lady Luck must be on my side.)
- I filmed a drama last year.
- Okay.
It's a short one.
- It has eight episodes.
- What about it?
It's going to premiere in September.
On SBS?
No, on an online streaming platform.
I see. But what about that?
- This episode will air in August.
- That's right.
- What a great PR chance.
- You can promote the drama.
(He can promote the drama at the perfect timing.)
- It's called, "Your Personal Taxi."
- He sure is lucky.
I'm a taxi driver in the drama.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He's so lucky.
- So...
to explain the plot...
You guys can just add in the information.
It's so complicated to describe the plot.
(As you requested, we're adding this in.)
(A feel-good music drama where a taxi driver listens to...)
(his passengers' stories and comforts them)
(Tae Hyun's upcoming drama will premiere soon.)
Well, this worked out for me.
Right, it did.
It's an 8-episode series at 30 minutes each.
- I want to talk to Ki Joo.
- It'll be short...
- Right. Ki Joo.
- Exactly.
I want to stop listening to you.
- I want to talk to her.
- Okay.
- Let's talk to her.
- Yes.
- I saw you and Tae Hyun...
- Me? Great.
walking toward us from a distance.
At first, I didn't know you guys were celebrities.
(They look like colleagues out for a stroll.)
I wondered if you were out for a stroll.
They were at ease.
- They were walking at ease.
- Right.
- They were so chill.
- That's right.
- You guys seemed so relaxed.
- Actually, Ki Joo...
- Yes.
- lives around here.
- I see.
- I'm familiar with this place.
This is her turf.
- I finally got to hear her voice.
- Yes.
- Is this like your hometown?
- Right.
- Yes.
- Really?
- Go on. Tell them.
- I come here...
- for a walk.
- Around Guui?
- I come here for a walk.
- Here?
- This place is great.
- There's a mountain too.
How long have you been living in Guui-dong?
At the beginning of my acting career,
my CEO used to live here.
He recommended this neighborhood.
I can easily go to beauty salons too.
- Really?
- You just have to cross the river.
You're talking about a different CEO, right?
- Yes. There was another CEO.
- Another CEO.
- She's with your agency now.
- Well,
let me give you some context about this CEO.
The CEO of her former agency...
- used to be In Sung's manager.
- Was he...
I see. Is that so?
When In Sung and I set up the company, he brought them too.
You joined their agency with the CEO too?
- I see.
- Then...
(That's how she joined his agency.)
I can't believe I got so lucky.
- Right. You...
- Jae Seok.
Do you know what's crazy now?
- I want to listen to her talk.
- Okay.
- Earlier...
- You need to stop talking.
I want to listen to her talk.
He took over the conversation after talking about...
- the former CEO.
- You can't give me an opening.
- We can't give him an opening.
- Yes.
Didn't a lot of people reach out...
- after your drama aired?
- Gosh, it's hot.
More people reached out to me than ever before.
- He also texted me really fast.
- When...
- Really?
- Yes.
Right. After "Teach You a Lesson,"
she got so many offers...
- for new roles. Okay.
- I want to hear it from her.
- Okay.
- We can't stop talking.
- I'll hear it from her.
- This is why.
We have to keep the conversation going.
Ki Joo, you need to teach him a lesson.
- Right.
- Gosh, no.
"Do not talk."
- Right. Teach him a lesson.
- Yes.
- You got many offers.
- What should I say?
- Yes, I got many offers.
- Right.
My friends also congratulated me.
Even people I haven't talked to for years congratulated me.
- They reached out to you.
- I see.
You and Yeon Seok have never worked on a project together.
- Right. We never worked together.
- Right. Probably not.
You guys have never met before?
- We met at awards ceremonies.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Gosh, awards ceremonies.
- What?
Yeon Seok starred in the drama,
- "Phantom Lawyer" this year.
- Yes.
- He did a fantastic job.
- Right. He was great.
I really enjoyed watching the drama.
Because of "Agent Kim Reactivated,"
- he won't get any awards this year.
- Hey.
- Why...
- Ji Sub totally killed it.
Why are you bringing that up now?
- Tae Hyun.
- He'll win the Grand Award.
- I...
- Come on.
I never thought I could win...
- the Grand Award.
- Listen.
- But it is a bummer.
- What do you mean?
- The ceremony hasn't even...
- You did a great job.
- It hasn't even started. Stop that.
- There's no mention of that now.
- How could he be so unlucky?
- You know what?
"Phantom Lawyer" did well too.
Exactly.
I might not have a shot with the year-end awards ceremony.
But I did win an award at an SBS awards ceremony.
I think they gave it to me proactively.
Then they don't want you to come to the awards ceremony.
(A spot-on analysis)
My gosh.
They already handled it.
Nominating him would be tough too.
Do you collect gossip about our industry...
and spread it?
- Hey.
- Gossip about the TV industry?
Gosh, that's a great way to handle it.
- They already gave me an award.
- This guy...
That's the Grand Award for the first half of this year.
So...
Hang in there for the next season.
- I see.
We received some snacks for product replacement today.
My gosh. Look at that.
- Isn't this made of soybeans?
- My gosh.
- I saw the ad for this.
- Right. It's not made of flour.
Since this is my fifth appearance, the show got an offer...
- for product replacement.
- There are several flavors.
The offers keep rolling in.
I want to try the cheese flavor.
- There are several flavors.
- Actually, they only used...
- soybeans to make this.
- Okay.
It makes a great meal replacement.
- There are many flavors.
- Macadamia and lemon.
There's a cheese flavor.
- It's tasty.
- Yes.
- It's also tasty.
- It's slim.
- This is good.
- What flavor is it? Chocolate?
- Yes.
- I should've gotten that.
I'm getting a slight hint of apple.
You go ahead.
Actually, this with yogurt would be enough...
for breakfast.
- Right.
- This is it.
It's my favorite flavor.
- Almond with chocolate.
- Almond. Yes.
I'll take this with me and have it later.
It's good.
The blueberry ones are good too.
- No. Give me almond with chocolate.
- I'll eat that instead.
- Give me almond with chocolate.
- There's no more.
- You put it in your pocket.
We ran out of that flavor.
- It's right here. You have it.
- Come on. Let go.
- You have it here.
- I want to eat it.
You have it right here.
- I'm going to have that later.
- Come on.
Leave it.
- Gosh. You...
- You're too old for this.
You can have more next time.
You'll film the next episode too.
I won't.
I put it in my pocket for later. Why did you take that?
Jae Seok's arch nemesis is here today.
Tae Hyun and In Sung tire me out. Seriously.
- They tire me out.
- Jae Seok's arch nemesis.
Wait. You know what this show is about, right?
Yes. I watched this show often.
You have to be good at games.
Right. We're in trouble.
Between your upper and lower bodies, which one are you...
- My upper body is slightly better.
- more comfortable with?
- Your upper body?
- I see.
Then let us play table tennis today.
We'll have to see what kind of game they prepared.
All right. We'll be filming in Ki Joo's hometown...
- today.
- Right.
Let's go and meet our Whenever Guests.
- I see.
- Read it.
Her name is Park Jung Hwa.
"Pop, pop, pop. We're crazy about that popping sound."
What's that?
"We see each other throughout the week."
"But we don't know each other's age, job, or neighborhood."
- What?
- "Exactly after an hour,"
"we drift apart, just a touch further."
"Will this be a chance for us to get closer?"
- Are they in a club or something?
- "Pop?"
They drift apart a touch further?
But they see each other all week.
"We see each other throughout the week."
(It's hard to figure out Whenever Guest's identity.)
They drift apart a touch further exactly an hour later?
- What's that about?
- Where is it?
It takes 17 minutes on foot.
We can take our time and walk there.
- My gosh.
- Do we get a lot of time...
to practice?
- What?
- Can we...
We don't know what game it is. So we can't practice.
- We can practice before the game.
- After they tell us what it is.
- But...
- Don't turn your back like that.
Hello.
- Hello.
- They're going on a walk.
I take it that Ki Joo hasn't filmed...
a lot of variety shows.
(She may be motivated, but she's new to variety shows.)
It's nice with the breeze.
It feels weird to be filming in my neighborhood.
- Right?
- Yes.
- To be honest, I feel uneasy...
- Left?
- to film shows in my neighborhood.
- Are you embarrassed? Right.
You feel the same way, right?
- Right, Ki Joo?
- Yes.
I feel perfectly fine...
- in other neighborhoods.
- Right.
- But I fear I might run into...
- It feels weird here.
my friends in my neighborhood.
- It feels weird.
- It does feel weird.
Ki Joo, do you walk around your neighborhood a lot?
If we go this way, we'll see Mount Acha.
- Right.
- When I want to climb Mount Acha,
- I'd walk through here.
- Right.
- What a beautiful neighborhood.
- It's nice.
(It's perfect for walks.)
Are you still a professor at Sejong University?
- He's still a professor.
- Right?
- The semester ended.
- I remember that.
- Yes. He said he'd be a professor.
- That's right.
The semester ended.
- Was it fun?
- It was fun.
It took me back to my college days...
- when I studied acting.
- I see.
And students like me too.
- I...
- Having him as a professor...
- That would be awesome.
- I bet they ask a lot of questions.
- I also give special lectures.
- Right.
You should invite Jae Seok for a special lecture.
Right. He totally should.
You should come for a lecture too.
Get him to do it first.
(Get Jae Seok to do it first.)
Since it's about acting, you should do it first.
Come on, Jae Seok. You act a lot on "Hangout with Yoo."
Hey, I just do comedy skits.
That's also acting.
Since we're on the subject,
- comedy acting is the hardest.
- It's the hardest.
- Right.
- Totally.
- You two can pull off...
- Right.
such a difficult task.
My gosh, you can't compare my acting to his comedy skits.
He's doing it without any foundation.
(In disbelief)
I analyze my characters...
- in other neighborhoods.
- Right.
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
You should say I analyze my characters...
and have a clear structure...
- and you don't have any foundation.
- Come on.
That's crazy talk.
- You don't even have a script.
- You just do whatever you want.
- Gosh, you ruined my morning.
Every word that comes out of your mouth is ruining my mood.
How dare you compare me to him?
(Chuckling)
From here...
What is it?
I think...
we're headed toward that sports center.
(Is he pointing at a community sports center?)
- Really?
- Wait. "Pop, pop, pop."
Then...
- is it an aerobics class?
- It's that way.
- I guess they exercise.
- It has to do with exercising.
- Wait. What makes a popping sound?
- Pop...
- "Pop, pop, pop?"
- Is it really table tennis?
My gosh. It's huge.
(The first Whenever Guest is at the community sports center.)
- It's a huge center.
- The sports center...
"Pilates." "Yoga." They've got everything here.
Wait. I smell a swimming pool.
Yes, me too.
Hello.
Gosh, there are so many people.
- Fourth floor.
- My gosh. Look at this place.
Oh, my. This place...
We have to go to the main gym on the fourth floor.
- The main gym?
- Is it basketball?
That's possible.
I got it.
- I think it's basketball.
- Let's go.
- It's not basketball.
- I hear small balls.
It sounds like badminton.
- It's a clean ball sound.
- Oh, this is it.
I see. It's the sport with those paddles.
- It's a trendy sport now.
- It's trending now.
Hello.
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- What's the name of this sport?
- What is it called?
- Pickleball.
- Pickleball?
- Yes.
- Pickleball.
I see.
(The first Whenever Guest: Park Jung Hwa)
This is a nice gym.
- It's big too.
- Isn't this a great gym?
People aren't that familiar with pickleball.
- Yes.
- So it combines many elements...
- of other sports, right?
- That's right.
- Table tennis and tennis.
- Table tennis, tennis,
- and badminton. Yes.
- Badminton? It combines...
elements of these three sports.
- Yes.
- That's right.
We're using a paddle just like in table tennis.
The rules are very similar to tennis.
- Really?
- Yes.
And the court is smaller, right?
- It's like a badminton court.
- Right.
- The same as a badminton court?
- Yes.
Pickleball has only the good elements of those sports.
This sport is good for senior citizens.
I see. Really?
("Jin of BTS Is Hooked on Pickleball")
(Jin)
(Even BTS loves this sport.)
(V, j-hope)
(It started with Bill Gates, the 1st generation of players.)
(Even superstars are getting into pickleball.)
(To ride the global wave,)
(they trade shots and sweat it out day in and day out.)
(Here are today's first Whenever Guests.)
(The pickleball club at Gwangjin-gu Community Sports Center)
So do you guys meet up here at this time every day...
to play pickleball?
- Yes.
- Yes. We meet in the morning.
From Monday to Friday.
(The club meets up every morning.)
So have you been playing the sport for 1 or 2 years?
I've been playing for two years now.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I've been playing for 7 months.
- It's been 7 months?
Who introduced you to this club?
My sister-in-law.
Your sister-in-law?
She told me it was really fun.
She said playing pickleball was really fun.
Where's your sister-in-law?
She plays somewhere else. We don't play together.
Right.
(A wise decision for both of their sakes)
- I see. Right.
- It won't be easy.
Playing together might be too much.
It might be too much.
What's so fun about pickleball?
You're willing to put aside time to play pickleball.
People who can't run well like me can still play.
- Really?
- Yes.
When I tried it out for the first time, it was so fun.
There isn't a place I can play this in my neighborhood.
I take the bus to come here. It takes an hour.
- She's so diligent.
- Sweating it out doesn't tire you.
- It actually boosts your energy.
- Yes.
- Right. It energizes me.
- That's true.
(It chases away fatigue and boosts their energy.)
You wrote you would bond for an hour while playing together...
- and then drift apart.
- You wrote you'd drift apart then.
- That's right.
- What does that mean?
That's true.
We stay focused for 1 hour and 20 minutes.
We're having so much fun then.
After we finish...
- "Goodbye."
(They're strangers once it's over.)
(A turn of events no one saw coming)
Really?
- But people usually...
- I see. You leave right away.
go out for lunch together...
- after exercising together.
- Yes.
I don't think we ever drank coffee together.
- Really?
- We don't know each other's age.
I'm quite curious about each other.
- You don't know each other well?
- No.
- We don't.
- I found out for the first time...
that her last name was Park.
- Totally.
- Right.
- Really?
- Yes.
(They finally find out about her last name...)
(when they see 5 days a week.)
Actually, this is quite common these days.
It's not just your club.
People meet up briefly to exercise together.
So people rarely ask personal questions.
- Not at all.
- We don't ask such questions now.
- Yes. That's true.
- In case they come across as rude.
Right. We say goodbye after playing pickleball.
- That's great.
- That's quite common these days.
But when you play sports together, you become curious about each other.
- "I wonder what she does."
- That's right.
- Right?
- Yes.
Are you the only guy in the club?
- He is.
- He's the only guy.
- Right.
I'm most curious about him. He seems unemployed.
- You're most curious about him?
- Like what he does for a living.
- What would you like to know?
- What he does for a living.
And why he joined our club.
- He's not here with his wife?
- Pardon?
How is he free around this time of the day?
- He came alone?
- I'm curious.
- No. She's my wife.
- He's my husband.
- I see. You're married. Right.
- Yes.
- The members are curious.
- They're married.
If you don't mind sharing,
could you tell us how you're free around this time of the day?
They're curious about that.
- I run a business.
- I see.
I try to clear my morning schedule.
- To play pickleball?
- It's really fun.
- I see.
- That's how it began.
- We had no idea.
- Me neither.
- It's my first time hearing it.
- It's fascinating.
What made you write to our show?
I heard this club was looking for new members.
So I signed up.
- At first, it felt awkward.
- Yes.
I wrote to the show,
hoping this would be a good chance to get to know each other.
- I'm sure they'll get closer...
- Yes. Right.
- after today.
- By the way,
do you guys have a team name or something?
- We have one.
- She named it.
- Yes.
- Did you name it? What is it?
- It's Play or Pass.
- Play or Pass.
- Play or Pass?
- Yes.
Do you guys have a team cheer?
- No.
- No team cheer.
- We're not so close.
- We're not close.
- They're not close.
That's the thing with the team cheer.
- We've never tried it.
- To do that,
- We have to get close.
- you guys have to bond first.
- Then you'd make one.
- Right.
(They're only serious about the sport.)
I bet the competition to get into your club is intense.
- There are barely any new openings.
- Right.
Everyone renews their membership.
- I bet. Exactly.
- Really?
- The waitlist is quite long.
- There's a long waitlist.
How can one join your club?
One of us has to get sick and leave.
One of you...
- Or we have to get injured.
- That's so true.
She has a point. I bet all of them are in pain.
But they're enduring the pain.
- Yes, that's true.
- That's true.
They can't be absent.
- They can't be absent.
- Yes.
"I'm not in pain."
- That's true.
- Yes.
- We can't get injured.
- Right.
There has to be an opening for new members to join.
- That's right.
- Yes.
We get to renew our membership first and local residents can join next.
Then residents from other areas can join.
- Hey, you can join the club.
- I should play too.
- Do you live in Gwangjin-gu?
- Yes.
- You should play.
But you said there was no opening.
No, she can leave.
(Risking his life for the solution)
You...
You have to be careful with what you say.
Okay.
(A shocking strategy to switch members)
(Withdrawing voluntarily)
- We won't keep filming here.
- I made a mistake.
- She's laughing now.
- Once we leave...
- Her feelings might be hurt.
- My gosh.
Is it possible for us to try playing pickleball?
- I'm curious. How do we play it?
- How do we play it?
- Let's try it.
- I'd love to try it.
- Ki Joo, are you athletic?
- I'm so not athletic.
- You got this!
We got this!
Wait.
(Bouncing the ball to check)
Bounce it before you serve.
Nice.
(He swings and misses.)
Hey.
This isn't easy.
Nice.
It feels different.
- My gosh.
- It doesn't bounce as much.
- Once we get used to doing this, - Right.
(She's done analyzing the paddle.)
doing a backhand shot might be difficult.
It's not easy.
- You got this.
- You can do it.
Ki Joo, you don't have to hit it hard.
- Yu Jae Seok. Yes.
- Nice.
(As Jae Seok and Yeon Seok engage in a rally...)
- Hit it!
- They're good.
- Nice.
Hit it!
- Try again.
- That's great.
My gosh. Wait.
They're pretty good, though.
Jae Seok is great.
This is fun.
Hey, this is fun.
Nice.
- Nice.
(The rally between Jae Seok and Yeon Seok is stable.)
- Great. You guys are great.
- He got it.
You guys are great.
Get it.
(Floundering to hit it back rather late)
Ki Joo isn't that athletic.
She said her upper-body control was better.
- This isn't easy.
- Try it.
(Tailoring his serve for Ki Joo)
- Nice.
- Try it, Ki Joo.
(This is the lady with better upper-body control.)
- Ki Joo.
- Just hit it once.
Just once.
I'm sorry.
If this ends up being our game, things will get tough.
Hitting the ball feels so satisfying.
Here comes the important part.
Hopefully, we can do well...
- and give them good presents.
- What is it?
This is Round One.
- My gosh.
- What?
I just saw it.
- You got this!
- Break the cookie.
- Break it.
And check it.
- What is it?
- I see a lot of stuff.
- What's this?
- I'm curious.
- What is it?
"We'd like to get to know each other..."
"with a cool glass of water after our workout."
"Nine team tumblers."
Nine tumblers.
(Their first group item, Stanley tumblers)
- Tumblers.
- It's nine tumblers.
(Cheering)
- My gosh. These are good tumblers.
- They're good tumblers.
- Really?
- They look so cute.
- I wanted them.
All right. What matters most next is the game we'll play.
(One-Touch Pickleball)
(Rally the ball back and forth and put it in the bucket.)
(But a player cannot hit the ball consecutively.)
(The time limit is 20 seconds.)
(The bucket)
In the end, getting it in the bucket...
- will be important.
- That's the hard part.
My gosh.
(They must get the ball in the bucket while rallying.)
My gosh. This is going to be tough.
We're counting on you, Jong.
- Yoo Yeon Seok!
- I'm good at games like this one.
- Right.
- Yes.
- He's good with ball games.
- He's good at ball games.
- He's tying his shoelaces too.
- He's super cool.
- It's all about the arms.
(Gazing affectionately)
I'll try my best.
(On the other hand, Ki Joo...)
To start... Ki Joo has to hit the ball at least once.
- To start...
- Ki Joo should start.
- She must hit it at least once.
- Yes.
- She should start.
- Right.
- You must hit it at least once.
- Try it.
Try it, Ki Joo.
Try it here.
- She can start us off on a course.
- Let's start.
- I'll pass it to you.
- Yes.
We only get 20 seconds?
Nice. You're killing it!
Ki Joo, you have to come closer.
- Come here.
- I should?
- Then I just hit the ball twice.
- You can't do that.
- So when I...
- I see. We can't hit the ball...
- consecutively?
- We can't do that.
Someone else must hit the ball after me.
Let's pretend we made it here.
- Okay.
- Let's pretend that we did.
- Putting it in the bucket...
- In the end,
- Try it in front of the bucket.
- this will be the hard part.
- Should we practice this step?
- Try it.
- Gosh.
- You should've come closer.
- You...
- You should've gotten it.
You should've hit it.
I keep finding myself...
- to leave the ball to you guys.
- Right.
- To us?
- I keep doing that...
- when I'm here.
- Watch.
(Play or pass?)
- See? We did it again.
- Ki Joo, you have to hit the ball.
- We can't do that.
- Hit the ball.
- You have to hit the ball.
- Should we call it?
- Yes.
- Let's say I'm standing here.
- I'm responsible for this area.
- Okay.
- Like this?
(That's cool!)
- Great.
- That's great.
See if you can put it in.
- Try it. See if you can put it in.
- Go ahead.
(We must be responsible for our own area.)
(She's fully focused.)
(Flinching)
We have to be gentle now.
(I'll guard my area.)
We have to be gentle now. Hit it gently.
Hit it gently.
(They fail again.)
- At this point...
- Someone has to take over then.
- Someone has to finish it well.
- This is the tough part.
I bet this is difficult even for us.
- Right. This might be...
- Of course, it's hard for us too.
- hard even for skilled players.
- It looks hard.
- This is way too hard.
- Is that the problem?
(It bounces off the bucket.)
You should've hit that.
- Try it.
- You can still hit the ball...
when it bounces off the bucket.
You can still hit the ball.
Okay.
- Try it.
- Okay.
- So here we are.
- Come on, do something.
- We need to slow down here.
- Okay.
Here.
- We should...
- Try to put it in the bucket.
Someone try it.
(Locked in)
- Try to put it in...
- You did it.
Okay.
Okay. We must try to get the ball in.
- Right. We have to think that.
- Once we get here. Yes.
- Let's try it.
- Okay. Let's go for it.
You know what? It doesn't matter which round we're at.
We must succeed...
- and give them the presents.
- Exactly.
If we end up losing the presents...
(Episode 1, their 1st spare time)
(Failed)
(Episode 1, their 2nd spare time, failed)
(Episode 2, their 1st spare time)
(Failed)
(They also failed the game during their 2nd spare time in Episode 2.)
(This season has been marred by failure.)
- Let's do a group cheer.
- Let's go.
- You got this.
- You can do this.
- One, two, three. Let's go!
Let's try Round One.
Play or Pass.
(The real game begins now.)
- We have a time limit.
- We must hurry.
Let's do this!
- Let's go!
- You got this.
- Let's go.
You can hit it forward.
- Round One.
- I'll run and hit it.
- In 1, 2, 3. Here we go.
- Here we go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(They've failed every game up until last episode.)
(However, their lucky charm, Tae Hyun, is here.)
(1st try)
- Hold on.
- Here.
Be gentle now.
(Look at that!)
That was so close.
Go for it.
- That was close.
- That was so close.
We almost had it.
- It's okay!
- We were so close.
- We can't get too excited there.
- How many seconds did we use?
We can't get too excited at the bucket.
- You used 11 seconds.
- We used 11 seconds.
Don't get too excited at the bucket.
Hey, this is way too hard.
It's so hard for Round One.
This is really hard for Round One.
What do you think, Ki Joo?
- I need to calm down.
- Hey, we can't get too excited.
I must say something about your eyes.
I saw resentment toward the player who hit the ball before you.
Let's stay calm.
Don't get too excited. Don't resent the others.
- Okay.
- Don't leave the ball to others.
- My gosh. This is hard.
Don't leave the ball to others.
- Don't leave the ball to others.
- Right.
Let's go for it.
- In 1, 2, 3. Here we go.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
- Let's do this.
- Was my serve okay earlier?
- Are we doing it?
- Just now...
- Yes, it was good.
(2nd try)
What? Is it mine?
- Gosh.
- Okay.
Wait.
(2nd try)
Jae Seok.
- We did it!
- Yes!
(Tae Hyun puts it in the bucket!)
- We did it!
- Yes!
Cha Tae Hyun!
Great job.
(Giggling)
- I knew it.
- Great job.
- He's our lucky charm.
- My gosh.
- I knew you could do it.
- He's our lucky charm.
(Lucky Charm Cha scores again.)
- Lucky Charm Cha.
- My gosh.
- Cha Tae Hyun!
- I knew it.
- All right.
- Round One, success!
- Success!
- What a thrill. No?
- My heart is racing.
What a thrill.
We didn't leave the ball to others.
- That was great.
- Great job.
Great work.
- All right.
- We succeeded on our second try.
- Yes.
- We're off to a great start.
- Yes. This is great.
- Here's what I observed.
- It's great.
I know we met for the first time today.
You guys hugged each other.
(The great level of physical interaction in the team's history)
- They moved one step closer.
- They got closer.
- It was our first group hug.
- That's right.
- It's our first hug.
- Yes.
- I love it.
All right. Round Two is next.
You must decide whether you want to go for Round Two...
- or stop here.
- Gosh. We succeeded way too early.
- Gosh. They'll go for it, right?
- They must go for Round Two.
- Gosh. This is...
- I think...
- We'll go for it.
- Let's go for it.
- You won tumblers for now.
Winning the presents from Round Two might be big enough.
- Yes.
- "Stronger teamwork."
"We need a team uniform to bring us together..."
"as a team."
- "Nine team uniforms."
- Team uniforms?
- Nine team uniforms. My gosh.
- I love it.
(Round 2 present: 9 workout outfits from Nike)
(Intense reaction)
- It comes in mint.
- Mint.
(Touched)
You got this!
- Team uniforms...
- You can do this!
- What's Round Two?
- Let's go!
(Round 2)
(The bucket will get smaller.)
(The bucket from Round 1...)
(will shrink to one-third of its size.)
That's so small.
(Speechless)
- But the thing is...
- It's smaller than my palm.
It's super tiny.
- Try it.
- So we're here.
- Yes, we're here.
- I'll pass it to you.
- Yes.
Here it is.
We must drive it to the bucket.
Tae Hyun, let's go. Let's go for it.
- Go!
This is great. We have great teamwork right now.
I have a good feeling. Let's do this.
The third try.
- Here we go!
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
(Exclaiming)
(3rd try)
Sorry, Yeon Seok.
- Okay.
- We got hyper.
- We did.
- Too hyper.
- We got a little too hyper.
- Exactly.
- But...
- We got hyper.
- Ki Joo, go a little slower.
- What...
The first shot was too strong.
- Ki Joo is a little...
- I got excited.
too excited.
(Calming down)
Don't push it off.
- Keep your head up.
- Ki Joo's hair is blowing.
Okay.
- Let's try again straight away.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. Here we go.
- Here we go.
Ready.
(4th try)
Nice. Slowly.
Good.
- That's it.
- Corner it.
(Someone...)
(must get the ball in.)
- That's it.
- Corner it.
(4th try)
(Yoo Yeon Seok got the ball in!)
(A second hug)
Well done.
Okay.
(Yoo One Shot is back.)
- Good job.
- My heart is pounding.
- That was the best.
- Round Two,
- success!
- Success!
Thank you!
Gosh, that just now was...
To think we'd succeed.
When the ball went in just now,
I saw it in slow motion.
(Bragging about his battle)
- I saw it.
- All right.
- Think carefully.
- This is bad.
We succeeded a little too early.
Here's the thing. We still have the chance.
- Right.
- Please think wisely.
- Think carefully.
- Yes.
The level of difficulty gets harder.
- Go big or go home?
Okay, think really carefully.
(Think about it again.)
- We got two steps...
- Right.
closer right now.
If we fail the last round...
- We'll forever grow apart.
- Exactly.
- Okay.
- Okay. Go or stop.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
Honestly, the vibe says we should keep going.
- True.
- It's a go.
- We can't stop here.
Round Three.
- Please.
- Pick a good one.
- What is it?
- Gosh.
- What does it say?
- I'm excited.
- What?
- Oh, my.
- Really?
- Oh, my gosh.
(Surprised)
- What? What is it?
- What?
- Unbelievable.
- Is it a car?
What is it?
Listen.
"I want to have a first get-together..."
"with the members of Team Play or Pass."
"One thousand dollars for a get-together."
(1,000 dollars for a team get-together)
Right here.
(And even in cash!)
We can have a meal together.
Team Play or Pass's first get-together.
- Correct.
- Right?
- We want one!
- Good.
- Oh, my gosh!
We still have the chance left.
-What's the mission?
(Round 3)
(Switching the goalpost to a plastic bottle)
(Knock over the plastic bottle to succeed.)
It's a completely different mission.
Do we knock it over?
Hit it, is it?
(Round 3 is knocking the plastic bottle over.)
- Wait.
- Isn't this better?
- Knocking it over may be better.
- Try it. This one's better.
Isn't this easier?
- It looks doable.
- Right?
Even a slight touch will knock it over.
- Give it a shot.
- Good.
Here.
(Succeeded in the first practice round)
See? It's easy.
Hit it up.
(Feeling smug)
- We've got it.
- They can do it.
It's a success.
Cut it.
- Change it.
- We're going to succeed, okay?
- Are you fine with this?
- Okay.
Change it to getting it in the bottle.
Or getting the ball on top.
Should we get the ball on the cap?
Are you really fine with it?
- All right. Let's give it a shot.
- Will they be fine?
- Right away?
- Yes. We did it just now.
Aren't we being too rash?
The fifth try. We have the chance.
Right, we still have the chance.
- Okay.
- We have the chance.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
- It's the fifth try, right?
- Yes.
Here we go.
That's more than enough.
(5th try)
(Tae Hyun saved it!)
(Ki Joo's out-of-the-park home run)
Well done.
- No, nice save.
- Good job.
- It's okay!
- No, nice save.
- Good job.
- It's okay!
- Good luck!
- Let's do this!
Good luck, Ki Joo!
We have tries 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10 left.
- Let's stay calm.
- Stay calm.
Don't get hyper.
- It's kind of...
- Shall we practice?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- This is when...
- Let's practice...
- we should practice.
- and calm down.
- Okay.
- We got too excited...
- after succeeding.
- We became conceited.
- It's the perfect time to practice.
- Okay.
All right.
Ready. Set. Go.
(Getting to the goalpost is easy.)
It's tough.
- We should corner in a bit more.
- This is tough.
- Do I serve?
- Yes.
- Yes, be proactive.
- Good.
- Yes.
- Proactively.
Being proactive is good.
- Again.
- Be proactive.
(Stunned)
You're not angry, are you?
Is it to teach me a lesson?
(It's a misunderstanding.)
- Ki Joo.
- Proactively.
Again. Try it.
Go for it.
(Screaming)
(Today's target?)
(The two have poor aim.)
- It was too far.
- Oh, dear.
- Aim closer.
- In short,
hit it from around here. Give it a shot.
- It'd be best to hit it...
- That's right.
- when the ball is around here.
- Try it.
- Let's aim to pass it to Yeon Seok.
- Okay.
- Try to hit it, Yeon Seok.
- Got it.
Proactively.
- Nice one.
- Yeon Seok's good at hitting it.
Let's go for it. Come on.
Let's try it. It'll be fine.
Okay, I've got a good feeling.
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
Here we go, okay? In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(7th try)
Okay, corner in.
Corner in.
(A chance for Yeon Seok)
(Into Ki Joo's arms)
Yeon Seok was aiming for the bottle. That was so close.
This is a tough one.
(Seventh try failed)
What a bummer.
Tries 8, 9, and 10, right?
Eight, nine, and ten.
- We'll use the chance.
- Do you want to use it?
- Chance!
Chance!
- Do I pick one?
- Yes.
(Spare chance)
Okay, read it for us.
(4 lucky boxes, 1 unlucky box)
- What does it say?
- "Change tools."
- Change tools.
- Hold on.
- It says "unlucky."
- It's unlucky.
- Unlucky?
- See those?
There are poop emojis on it.
Why poop, of all things?
(Changing the tools to rice paddles)
Everyone?
All of us?
(All members' tools change in this round.)
For real?
(Picked the one unlucky box)
- Oh, no.
I picked the wrong one.
- It's okay.
We might succeed with these.
- Exactly.
- Right?
Try the table tennis balls.
The ball might bounce less.
(Skilled)
It's not bad.
- Yeon Seok's good at it.
- He's good.
Totally.
But Yeon Seok's always good.
Even with the table tennis ball.
The surface area is small,
but it's not that bad.
(Tae Hyun has gotten used to the rice paddle.)
(Ki Joo got used to it in no time.)
Let's give it a shot. We can do it!
- We can do it!
- Good luck!
Let's give it our best.
- Is it the eighth try?
- Eighth try.
- Here we go!
- Go low.
- Come on! We can do it!
- Good luck!
Good luck. You can do it!
Set.
(8th try)
Mine.
They could succeed.
(8th try)
- Nice.
- Ki Joo.
(Failed)
Ki Joo.
(Screaming)
(The 8th try ended on a close call.)
It's okay.
- It's okay!
Don't worry. We're back to normal now.
- Darn.
- We're back to normal.
- It's fine.
- Let's get rid of this fast.
- This doesn't work.
- Get it out of my sight.
- We're back to our paddles.
- Yes.
They're back.
- The paddles are back.
- Loosen up.
- We can do it!
- Good luck!
- Let's do a group cheer!
- Come.
- The mood is pretty low.
- Good luck!
- Here.
- Play or Pass, we can do it!
- We can do it!
All right.
- The mood has gotten low. Ki Joo.
- I can do it.
- Let's do this.
- Think of it as table tennis.
- Try to hit it if you get a chance.
- Let's try it lower.
- Ninth try.
Round 3, 9th try. Let's do this!
- Good luck!
- We must succeed.
- Ready.
Do we go for it? In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
Please, we want a get-together.
Set.
- Easy on the way there.
- Yes.
I shouldn't have left it.
Oh, my gosh.
(Ace Tae Hyun's huge mistake)
Only one try left.
- Oh, no.
- It's okay.
No, this is bad.
There's only one try left.
It's driving me crazy.
We're on the last try.
Let's do this!
- Good luck!
(The shadow of failure looms once again.)
- Hey, Yeon Seok.
- Let us have a get-together.
- Let's practice, Tae Hyun.
- We should do it, no matter what.
- No.
- Look at the mood.
(Special training)
- Good luck!
- We should practice.
- Let's practice. It won't work.
- Practice?
- Are we practicing?
- Yes.
- You can do it.
- Practice round.
I'm seeing those eyes from...
- "Teach You a Lesson."
- Really?
- Ki Joo's eyes have changed.
- Yes, they have.
Let's try again.
(Practicing until they succeed)
That was so disappointing.
Go down.
Again. Oh, dear!
They're going all out.
I know, right?
- Please.
- Yes, proactively like this.
(The last practice without a break)
That's it.
Nice.
- Go low.
- Yes.
- Here.
- Keep it low.
- Nice.
- Here.
Nice!
Nice.
Yes, just like this.
- We can do it.
- Just like this.
- Stay strong.
- We can do it.
Save the ball, no matter what.
- Save the ball, no matter what.
- Last try. Let's cheer.
- Let's go!
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's do this!
Come on. Please.
- I'm nervous.
- Please.
- Play or pass, do not hesitate.
- Okay.
- Just go for it.
- Proactively.
- Here we go, okay? In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
The last try. Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
Ready.
Stay strong.
Save the ball, no matter what.
(The last try with everything on the line)
(Last try)
- Okay.
- Tae Hyun.
- Sorry.
- Oh, no.
- Here.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
(Reset)
(Last try)
(Yeon Seok saved it!)
Nice!
(Jae Seok's final one shot!)
(A miraulous success on the last try)
We did it!
(Yu Jae Seok's goodbye home run)
(The perfect teamwork led to success.)
They did it!
We can have a meal together!
(Crying)
- That was amazing.
- Round Three,
- success!
- Success!
(Round 3 success)
The last shot...
It was the winning smash.
You did it.
(Jae Seok is the best!)
You did it, Jae Seok.
I hit it thinking it was all or nothing.
Amazing!
I remember nothing after I dove for the ball.
- I can't.
- I can't remember anything since.
(The season's first success after they threw themselves into it)
It's the first dopamine rush after months.
- It sure gave us a dopamine rush.
- Totally.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Play or Pass.
Congratulations on even securing the get-together money.
(Won tumblers, team uniforms, and get-together money)
- Thank you.
- Oh, my gosh!
- I'm on the verge of crying.
- With this,
you must have a get-together.
- Right?
- Yes.
- It'll help you get along.
- Absolutely.
How was it today?
It feels like a dream. I'm about to cry. Oh, dear.
I hope our team and coach...
- Yes, together.
- stay together for a long time.
(Getting emotional again)
It's as if...
she has won in a pickleball competition.
- It's like a winner's speech.
- This is way better than winning.
I agree.
We can finally have a get-together.
- Right?
- Thank you so much.
Whenever possible,
- play or pass!
- Play or pass!
(We've gotten close.)
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Take care.
(After wrapping up the first spare time on a happy note)
(Groaning)
Unbelievable.
What a relief.
- It's a relief we succeeded.
- For real.
It's a big relief.
(In a daze)
You know...
When the first hit failed, I thought it was over.
- But the ball was saved...
- I don't even know how it happened.
- Right?
- The next moment,
- we had succeeded.
- Someone tried, right?
- It felt like...
- Really?
The ball bounced off...
- of something, right?
- I tried.
(Jae Seok's 1st try failed as the ball bounced off the box)
- Ki Joo saved it.
- I remember it now.
- Tae Hyun hit it.
- Yes.
(Jae Seok's finishing hit)
I got the ball.
Either way, my knees hurt when it was over.
I don't know what happened.
(Reason behind the pain)
Every time Tae Hyun is on the show, we miraculously succeed.
That's right.
He sure is the one-of-a-kind gem of this show.
Am I? Am I a gem?
(A one-of-a-kind gem trove of luck)
We deserve something delicious.
Let's have something good.
Ki Joo is...
- Ki Joo...
- Sorry?
is exhausted.
(Semi-conscious)
Didn't you know a good place, Ki Joo?
(A local spot to refuel)
A nearby place serves both...
kalguksu and bossam.
It's in that direction from here.
- Is it far from here?
- They serve kalguksu,
kongguksu in summer,
- Let's go there.
- and bossam.
That'd be better.
(Setting off immediately)
The excitement I felt from succeeding isn't cooling down.
It's not.
(Leaving triumphantly for the first time this season)
- We...
- It's still hard to believe.
- Seriously.
- Let's calm down with some food.
I'm starving.
- Are you?
- Yes.
- The hunger is really hitting now.
- It's about time we got hungry.
- It's that time of the day.
- It's only natural.
(Staring)
It must be cool in there.
Where?
In that store.
- Do you feel hot?
- Yes.
(The type to talk to herself loudly)
(They made it to the bus stop in the heat.)
It's the way from there.
Gwangjang-dong Hyundai Apartment.
- Two stops.
- Two stops?
The bus will be here in 1 to 2 minutes.
- Actually, in five minutes.
- We have five minutes?
No, wait.
Five minutes.
Isn't that also a kalguksu place?
- Where?
- Up ahead.
The one next to the gas station.
- Deungchon Shabu Kalguksu?
- Yes.
- Or how about house-made galbi?
- Shall we go?
- House-made galbi?
(Already looking elsewhere)
- Or over here?
- Where?
Walkerhill?
- Pizza Hill?
- Pizza?
- I haven't tried it yet.
- Shall we have pizza?
- I heard it was famous.
Yes, it's famous. The pizza is quite pricey.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Isn't the loser of the game...
- It's really expensive.
going to pay for the meal?
- We...
- Are we getting pizza?
Should we just go?
We succeeded. Don't we deserve something nice?
- Wait.
- I've heard about...
the place but haven't been yet.
(Should we raise the stakes?)
But going to the next spot afterward from Pizza Hill...
is going to be a hassle.
- True.
- It's too far.
- It'll be a real hassle.
- For sure.
I'll pay for all four of us.
Okay.
- All right.
- Up I go.
- To the back?
- Okay.
(Yelping)
You make a lot of sound effects, Ki Joo.
Gosh.
Sitting down sure is nice.
Right?
- We needed a break.
- Yes.
We ran at least 5,000 steps.
Already?
Pickleball is indeed a workout.
- It looked fun.
- It's actually fun.
- Pickleball?
- What we played was more fun.
Tell the team to try it.
(Highly satisfied with the game)
- They will get along much faster.
- Totally.
To get to know the members, that game...
- The best one.
- is the best.
But you know,
a casual relationship like theirs isn't all that bad.
- It's great.
- Exactly.
- Get to know what someone does, - Right.
and they'll just ask for money.
They'll only cause trouble.
We need to walk a little from here.
- A four-minute walk?
- Yes.
Is it raining?
To the left.
Ki Joo should know the way from here.
- Yes, I do.
- You do, right?
Yes, I know the way.
We're almost there.
Yes. We just have to turn at that corner.
- Great.
- Correct.
(A familiar restaurant she can find without a map)
It's visible from here.
- Where?
- That kalguksu place.
It's over there.
That looks good.
Is it all right? Yes?
- It looks great, Ki Joo.
- Come on.
- Hello.
- Gosh. Hello.
(Entering the kalguksu place)
- I love it.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
- Why are you groaning?
(Scanning the menu)
They have many kinds of kalguksu.
Gosh. There are so many.
We should get bossam.
- Of course, we should.
- Mung bean bindaetteok is good.
Bossam's tasty too.
There's napa cabbage soup too.
It's tasty.
- Is the soup good?
- Yes.
- Let's order what each wants.
- Sure.
What about you, Tae Hyun?
I'll have 2 bites of kongguksu and 2 bites of kalguksu.
(Booing)
Do you want to share them with me, then?
- Order two of each, then.
- Let's share.
- Two kalguksu and...
- Yes.
Order one of each for them to share.
- Shall we?
- Two kalguksu.
- Could we order now?
- Yes.
Two kalguksu made with ox bone soup.
And two kongguksu.
And will a medium bossam be enough for us?
Aren't you going to have the mung bean bindaetteok?
- I was thinking...
- I'm going to have it.
- Ma'am.
- One mung bean bindaetteok, please.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(Satisfied)
- Gosh. I'm so sleepy.
- Goodness.
You are tired.
- We worked up a sweat earlier.
- Gosh.
- That game required lots of energy.
- Yes.
- We practiced a lot too.
- That's right.
It's nice and cool.
Ki Joo turned away and yawned just now.
She was like this.
(I saw it.)
(Ratting her out right away)
- It's because she's exhausted.
- She must be.
It's because you're suddenly relaxed.
- Really.
- Tonight,
you'll suddenly think of this when you're in bed.
(I was in bed, but suddenly)
Actually, "Suddenly" by I.O.I...
has never sounded this stale before.
(The bright, refreshing song by the girls...)
(suddenly became stale.)
Suddenly
How could it sound so stale?
- It's a bit...
- Wait.
This old song also has a similar melody.
How does it sound?
(The middle-aged man at the flower shop is pretty)
He couldn't be prettier
(While they are searching for the pretty flower shop man...)
- It's here.
Put it away.
- Goodness.
- Okay.
This is what old men do.
(The old men 1 and 2 who clapped)
It's for no reason.
- Why did we clap?
- You and I did.
I clapped because you did. Okay?
- These old men.
- Why did you clap?
It was just the two of us.
(An old man always thinks he's not an old man.)
Gosh. Thanks for the food.
- Ki Joo, I'm excited.
- Yes.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
Gosh, this is crazy.
When you look at the side dishes,
- This is a legit place.
- you can tell this place is good.
It's a good restaurant.
Let's see.
(Trying a piece of meat first)
- Goodness.
- I'll try it like this.
It's tasty.
It's chewy.
It's good.
- It tastes good.
- Yes.
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
I'll have it with bossam kimchi.
(Its chewiness is so satisfying.)
- I'll take this.
- Gosh.
- I'll put it here.
- I'll have it with bossam kimchi.
It's good.
(He makes a great wrap by topping it with ssamjang.)
Ki Joo, this is worth the bus ride.
- That's right.
- I'm glad to hear that.
(Eating while feeling proud)
(Chowing down)
- We should've ordered a large one.
- True.
Yeon Shik was right about it.
Do you work out, Ki Joo?
I lift weights and do Pilates often.
(Responding)
I box every now and then.
- Do you go boxing?
- And I swim occasionally.
Did you start boxing for a project?
- No. I did it to improve fitness.
- Gosh.
Thankfully, it was helpful when I shot "Teach You a Lesson."
- I can see that.
- That's right.
The actors who do action movies always do boxing.
I know.
Those are basically all cardio.
- It's here. Quit it now.
- It's here.
- Here's your kongguksu.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Here and here.
- It looks tasty.
- The noodles look tasty.
I must have noodles.
Now that it's here, I'm glad we ordered it.
Ki Joo insisted that we order it.
(Golden mung bean bindaetteok)
Okay.
(Trying the kongguksu first)
Actually...
Should we do it?
This kongguksu. It's strange, Jae Seok.
What? What is this?
(Slurping the noodles again)
(What is this?)
(He can't stop having this strange kongguksu.)
(Devouring the whole plate)
- Gosh. It's so good.
- Yes.
This place is awesome.
Usually, I'm not that into food.
Exactly.
- You don't savor food.
- Nothing's really that tasty.
- But it's really tasty here.
- This place is good.
Your favorite spot will become unavailable.
- It's a done deal.
- No.
I come here often, though.
That's right.
(Having another bite while she can)
This is a great spot.
(Devouring kalguksu too)
This is perfect.
Gosh, Ki Joo. Everything is good.
It's tasty.
- It's all thanks to you.
- I'm glad to hear that. It was far.
It's worth the bus ride.
Are you still not drinking?
- No.
- I see.
What about you, Ki Joo?
- I can't drink.
- Can't you drink at all?
I used to drink a little.
But since I haven't been drinking...
- You're intolerant.
- because I'm intolerant,
I get tipsy even from non-alcoholic drinks now.
- Really?
- Yes, it still has a little bit.
- That's right.
- When I come home after shooting,
I drink a can of beer,
and I love it.
That's good.
You can't say that because you don't know it.
It's good.
Beer, my foot.
(Responded so half-heartedly that it was shocking)
- Should we play a game now?
- Shall we?
Let's simply spin this.
And which part is the pointer?
What about this part?
- That's the pointer.
- It has to point to your body.
Let's take turns and spin it.
- Ki Joo will spin first.
- Okay.
- Me?
- Yes.
I'll spin it now. Spinning.
It's done.
- Hold on.
- It's over.
That was...
- It pointed at you.
- She threw it at me.
- There's nothing we can do.
- Hold on.
- We can't help it.
It should at least make one full turn.
- It made a full turn.
- Hold on.
- It made one full turn.
- Give it to me.
- It just made a full turn.
- It made a full turn.
Listen. She tossed it to me like this.
There's nothing to be upset about.
- I know.
- Right?
Okay. I'll pay.
- Thank you, Yeon Seok.
- Thank you.
It was good, Ki Joo.
(Upset Yeon Shik pays for lunch.)
We really enjoyed it.
- We enjoyed it, ma'am.
- Thank you.
It was really good.
Gosh. Us, the glasses-wearers...
My glasses are fogging up.
But is only one lens fogging up?
- Jae Seok.
- You're tearing up.
- You're so sly.
- Why?
You look like this.
- It's because...
- Why is only one side fogging up?
the AC blew on only one side.
- How could this happen?
- Look.
Only this side was getting the AC.
(The woes of wearing glasses)
- Do we walk?
- We have to. It's a 13-minute walk.
I love it.
(It's still fogged up.)
- Professor Yoo.
- Yes?
Thanks for lunch.
- Sure. It was really good.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Let's get going.
Yes, hello.
- Hello.
- Goodness.
How could he bow so politely?
There are many kids who are polite.
Usually, they say, "Hey, it's Yoo Yeon Seok!"
But they don't do that when they're alone.
- Is it when they're together?
- Two kids won't do that either.
- It starts from 3.
- It's when there are 3 or more.
- Gosh. He's adorable.
- Yes.
(Smiling like a dad)
- Are you a 5th grader?
- I'm a 6th grader.
- A 6th grader?
- You're a 6th grader.
Gosh. You have a smiley face.
You're so funny.
- Talk to us.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going home.
- You're going home.
You're waiting for your friends.
(Screaming)
- "It's Yu Jae Seok."
- I told you.
- I told you. It starts from three.
- Now, this is normal.
- So... Shall we?
- "It's Yu Jae Seok."
- When there are three or more, - I said...
they go, "It's Jae Seok."
I told you.
As soon as there were three...
They don't do that when there are just the two of them.
But when the three have gathered,
- "Gosh. It's Jae Seok."
- they go, "It's Yu Jae Seok."
He keeps bowing to us.
- Bye.
- He's cute.
He's shy.
(Good luck!)
(Bowing)
He cheered and bowed at the same time.
- He did it like this.
- "Good luck."
(He was 2 times cuter when saying goodbye.)
After turning right over here...
- Is it here?
- Yes. We turn right.
And we just need to climb up a little.
Gosh. Starting from here, it's a school zone.
Goodness.
Are we going to a school again?
Gosh. It's a school.
It's from Lee Tae Oh.
- Lee Tae Oh.
- Yes.
"I loved playing with my friends from first grade."
- "From first grade?"
- He must be a kid.
"I'm so sad because I can't play with them every day now."
"I want to be on Whenever Possible,"
"my favorite show in the whole universe,"
"with my friends, who I love the most in this world."
"I might even faint when I get to meet Jae Seok."
(Touched)
They are kids.
- Are they kids?
- We are bad around them.
- We have a jinx around them.
- We do have one.
- It's...
- Right?
As we said, we have trauma involving them.
- We're going inside the school.
- It's the young children again.
Yes.
(Failed at elementary schools in Episodes 27, 31, and 41)
(They walk along the alley.)
- It's a school.
- Gosh. No.
There's another turn.
It's Gwangjin Elementary School.
It's an elementary school.
(Anew, upright, and strong)
(The heroes of the future grow here.)
Gosh. This school is pretty.
(Checking the card)
It says "1-2" on here.
- It must be 1st grade, Class 2.
- They're 1st graders.
They're 1st graders.
Gosh. It's...
Let's do well here today.
- I already have an upset stomach.
- Are you nervous already?
- I'm already a bit...
- I have indigestion.
- We're right on time.
- Yes.
- We nailed the timing.
- We're on time.
I see some students.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You're so adorable.
- Bye.
(The polite students are heading home after school.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
Bye.
(Entering the school to a warm welcome)
- Bye.
- Is that it?
It's Class 1-2.
- It's 1st grade, Class 2.
- Yes.
- It's here.
- It's over here.
- This is it, right?
- Right.
- Who was our Guest?
- It's Class 1-2.
Lee Tae Oh.
- Tae Oh.
Gosh. Hello.
- Hello.
Who is Tae Oh who wrote the letter?
- Me.
- It's you. Goodness.
- What were you doing?
- Tae Oh.
We were playing Red Light, Green Light.
Gosh. We're in trouble. It's an emergency.
They are babies.
Are you first graders?
- We're 2nd graders.
- You're in 2nd grade now.
I see. You are second graders.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
That was...
- They're so polite.
- This school...
- isn't on summer vacation yet.
- I see.
- Is this when the school ends?
- So, they're heading home.
- Am I right?
- Yes.
They still had classes today.
Why don't we sit down and talk?
Here?
(Taking a break to set up)
What is that?
I don't know.
(Everything looks interesting.)
Gosh. What should I do with you?
You must be in different classes now, right?
- Yes.
- He and I are in the same class.
And they are in different classes.
Are Seo Jun and the rest in different classes?
- Yes.
- You talk so smartly.
From the looks of it, each class has...
How many students are there in a class?
- About 16 students.
- About 17.
About 16 to 17 students.
There's a tent in a class now.
How many classes are there?
- There are 4 classes.
- There are 4.
There are only four classes.
When I was in school,
- there were 15 classes.
- Stop talking about the past.
- Pardon?
- He's an old man.
He's a stuck-up old man, talking about the past.
That's a lot of classes, right?
- Yes.
- Right.
(Such a scale of the schools is unimaginable today.)
Tae Oh, were you in this class when you were in first grade?
- Yes.
- Now, you're in second grade.
- I see.
You became friends back then?
- Yes.
- Are you best buddies?
You all answer questions so well.
Are the four of you still best friends?
- Yes.
(Clear and concise again)
It's not easy to interview them.
They'll start talking after a while.
- You four are best friends.
- Yes.
Why do you think you're so close?
Because we played together when we were in first grade.
Okay.
- And we ate together too.
- That's right.
What about you, Seo Jun?
- We went to indoor playgrounds, - That's right.
and we rode bikes together.
- I see. That's why you bond.
- Yes.
(Tae Oh and his friends 1st met in 1st grade.)
(Their precious friendship has been building.)
What about you, Ha Yul?
Yesterday, we ate...
jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk together.
Did you? What about you, Jae Hyeon?
You're the last one. What do you say?
- We went to indoor playgrounds.
- I see.
We ate...
- jjajangmyeon together too.
- Right.
- And what else?
- Jjajangmyeon...
is what brought them together.
It's the Chinese restaurant.
- Jjajangmyeon is good.
- Yes.
That hasn't changed since we were kids.
- Jjajangmyeon tasted so good then.
- Yes.
What was your favorite food when you were young, Ki Joo?
I had lots of dakgalbi.
- Dakgalbi.
- Because you're from Chuncheon.
- Are you from Chuncheon?
- Yes.
- I see. It was dakgalbi.
- Usually,
we had our birthday parties at dakgalbi places.
It's different, isn't it?
- Club activities? Dakgalbi, it is.
- Dakgalbi.
(All gatherings happened at dakgalbi places.)
But who wrote the letter? Was it Tae Oh?
- Yes.
Tae Oh, what made you write the letter?
I started watching Whenever Possible since last year.
It was so fun, so I watched it every day.
- I see.
- Really?
Did you write the letter yourself? Or did your mom do it for you?
I told Mom...
that I wanted to be on the show too.
Mom said I couldn't be on the show.
But when I looked it up,
it said I could write a letter, so I did it.
- Did you look it up yourself?
- Yes.
Your mom said it was impossible.
But when you looked it up, it was all possible.
- So you wrote it.
- Yes.
- That's amazing.
- That's great.
Kids these days are extraordinary.
They're so brilliant and smart.
Did your parent say anything, Seo Jun?
About the shoot today?
They told me not to get edited out.
Don't edit him out.
- No. That's right.
- Don't edit Seo Jun out.
They told him not to get edited out.
Tae Oh, did your parents say anything else?
That I need to speak clearly.
- And to bow politely.
- Right.
The four of you bowed perfectly.
You said it was your dream to meet Jae Seok.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- How do you feel after meeting him?
- It's disappointing, isn't it?
Gosh. You were good, overlapping his answer.
He overlapped it in the best way.
- Do you find it interesting?
- Yes.
- Do you know...
- They don't know me.
what these men do?
I know you and Yeon Seok only.
- You know us.
- That's good enough.
These two are...
Right. You're too young...
to watch their works.
- They shouldn't watch them yet.
- If you watch them,
- They can't watch them.
- it's a bit...
Do you not know me when you watched this so many times?
- He played big roles.
- I was on the show four times.
I appeared in every season.
Okay.
"Okay."
He says he's all right.
By the way, Mom prayed...
that I'd be born cool like Yeon Seok.
- Really?
- For you, Tae Oh?
- When you were in the womb.
It seems like...
- your mom liked me.
- Yes.
What did she like about him?
- Because he was handsome?
- She found him cool.
- She must've watched your dramas.
- I...
So, your mom likes Jae Seok,
but it was Yeon Seok...
- That guy.
- who she wanted you to look like.
- I can't believe that guy.
- So,
she's realistic.
I have a question. Do you have a dream, Ha Yul?
I want to be a teacher.
- You want to be a teacher.
- A teacher.
- What about you, Jae Hyeon?
- A YouTube creator.
What about you, Seo Jun?
- A PE teacher.
- What about you?
- I want to go to Denmark...
and become a LEGO builder.
- A LEGO builder.
- I see.
- That's specific.
- That's very specific.
- Do you like building blocks?
- Yes.
- Are you good at it?
What have you made?
I made cars, houses,
(Tae Oh's works)
and a huge house.
Even a huge house.
- You're good with your hands.
- That's amazing.
So, these four children...
are Whenever Guests today.
Tae Oh, you probably know it if you have watched it.
When we shot with children,
we couldn't get any good results.
Have you seen us play games...
- on the show?
- Yes.
Do you think we're good at it?
They responded a beat late.
Did you have good dreams last night?
In my dream, I received a Nintendo on this show.
- Really?
- That's very specific.
A Nintendo game.
You got a present in your dream. My goodness.
The kids these days love Nintendo games.
They love them.
Now, let's...
Let's break the bad cycle...
for the children.
- Let's make it happen today.
- Seriously.
I really want to give presents to you, Tae Oh.
Okay. Round One.
Break the fortune cookie to check the present.
- Break it. Good.
- Good.
What's inside?
(Curious)
Please read it.
They look so curious.
"Even though we are in different classes now,"
"we are still best friends."
"Four North Face backpacks."
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- Backpacks.
- Four backpacks.
(The backpacks appear before their eyes.)
Gosh. What do you think?
- It's pretty.
- Is it pretty?
- They're the same.
- Their reaction...
- isn't that great.
- Gosh.
- It's matching backpacks.
- It's pretty, though.
This is nice.
- Is it all right?
- Yes.
Okay.
(An unfiltered reaction)
Maybe because it's related to studying,
they're not super excited.
They want game consoles.
Okay. What's the mission?
(Stick Them Together!)
(Each player will flick a magnet...)
(to stick it to a magnet marble.)
We have to stick it.
- Last time, we avoided sticking it.
- We avoided sticking it.
Back at the Nuclear Energy Center.
We need to stick it to the marble.
- This is new.
- This won't be easy.
- How does it work?
- We will flick them one by one...
- to stick it, right?
- Yes.
They have to stick together.
- I see.
- The next person...
- I stick them together like this.
- They have a strong magnetic force.
I think we'll be fine in Round One.
Try it, Ki Joo.
That's so easy.
- We'll give you a chance.
- No.
- Change it when you have a chance.
- Are you good?
There must be a trap.
- Suddenly, it'll become hard.
- There must be something.
Change it when I give you a chance.
Are you good?
It'll become super tough in Round Three.
- I'm sure there's something.
- Again?
It feels so easy.
- Listen, everyone.
- All right.
- You have your backpacks now.
- It's a done deal.
I think we're good, Tae Oh.
- Jae Hyeon, Seo Jun, and Ha Yul.
- Seo Jun looks relieved.
- Don't worry.
- You already won the backpacks.
- Okay. Let's do it.
- Let's try it.
- Okay. One...
- Let's...
In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go!
- Let's go!
That was a strong chant.
- I think we'll succeed.
- We will.
- Here we go.
You did a good job just now.
It was so easy just now.
- Let's do it in the same order.
- If it's easy, it's easy.
- There's nothing we can do.
- Yes.
- We might let our guard down.
- That's right.
Flick it lightly.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
- That's how it goes.
- Good. It's over.
- It was a nice start.
Yes.
It's a bit far from now.
I see. That's the hard part.
- It's okay.
- Do it, Ki Joo.
It has come to the center.
- It has come to the center.
- Okay. It's at the center.
You'll finish it, Jae Seok.
(Tae Hyun goes 3rd.)
What?
- What?
- Okay.
What?
We might be able to succeed.
- I just need to bring them close.
- It'll work.
- Why wouldn't it?
- Don't let your guard down.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- They'll pass.
- Hey.
If they get it on their first try, it's crazy.
- Okay.
- Come on.
(If he sticks this magnet to the marble,)
(they succeed Round 1.)
Sucess.
(They succeed on their first try.)
- Yes!
- Okay!
We did it.
- That was so easy.
- You're happy.
- Hey.
- Round One,
- success!
- Success!
(Round 1 success!)
- This is...
- You're happy.
Round One was so easy, though.
Wasn't it?
You all.
- What now? We succeeded.
- We succeeded in Round One.
- We'll give you the backpacks.
- The backpacks.
(Clapping)
- But...
- Let's go until Round Three.
as you might have seen,
if we fail Round Two, you can't take those backpacks.
- You should know that, okay?
- Yes.
- You all understand that, right?
- Should we proceed to Round Two?
Please say go or stop.
In 1, 2, 3...
- Go!
I have a good feeling.
Please read it.
Nintendo!
They all want the game console.
I think there might be one.
No?
"I want to be a LEGO builder."
"My favorite time is building blocks with my friends."
"Four LEGO sets."
(Present for Round 2, 4 block toys)
- Nice.
- That's good.
- They love it.
- That's...
- I love it.
- It's big.
- It's huge already.
- Goodness.
- Hold on.
- It's not an ordinary one.
- They have different kinds.
- I love that one.
- Hey.
- They're amazing.
- What?
- Yes.
- It's a tough one.
- Goodness.
- He's excited.
- What?
- Do you love them?
- His eyes have gone wide.
(His eyes open wide.)
Why don't you each hold one?
- Good.
- Yes, hold it.
Hey, it's heavy.
- Look at this.
- It's heavy.
- What do you think?
- It's so heavy.
- Nice.
- Hey,
- it's heavy.
- When we succeed Round Two,
we'll give them to you as a present.
Let's go!
- Let's do it!
- For now...
(Taking them back for now)
- They need to put them back.
- Why are you taking them back?
- Please put them back for now.
- Why?
For now. We'll get them by completing the mission.
We'll get them for you.
- We'll get them for you.
- This is so lovely.
- Jae Seok, can you promise them?
- Well...
- We have to make it happen.
- Let's do this.
I'm nervous.
(Round 2)
(The desk gets bigger.)
(Round 1)
(Round 2)
- It's bigger.
- I see.
(That means the magnets are farther away from one another.)
The one who is good at it should go first.
It's...
- You need to stick them together.
- It's moving outward.
- It is, indeed.
- It might fall off, then.
- That's true.
- Jae Seok, it's...
Yes. It can fall off, but...
(When the magnets fall off the desk, it's a fail.)
Hold on. Then I should flick...
It's farther away from the marble now.
Control your power.
(Failed)
- We're starting to fail now.
- But what if we do this,
- We can flick it that way.
- and we flick...
- We can do that.
- That's right.
Aim for the gap in between.
If it goes and sticks to them all, it'll work.
Now, it's getting nervous.
It's not that easy.
- Then, for this one...
- It's not easy.
Okay. Good. Let's try it.
Okay. Let's get it.
Let's chant together. Come.
In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go!
- Let's go!
Gosh. That was thunderous.
(Charged with energy)
We have to get LEGO blocks.
That's right. We have to win them.
- We can try it. We're good.
- We're going for it, right?
I won't go first.
- I won't go 1st.
- Jae Seok was good going 1st.
- I'm not confident to go 1st.
- You went 1st, and it was good.
- I won't go first.
- No, you did a great job.
I'm not confident enough to go first.
In 1, 2, 3,
- here we go.
- Here we go.
- Ki Joo should go first, then.
- Do you want to try it?
Okay.
She is brave.
(She bravely goes 1st.)
- Gosh. It went too far.
- Goodness.
- Hold on. We have to be strategic.
- Hold on.
Which magnet do we flick?
If you flick this one the wrong way,
it might fall off that way.
Isn't it better to flick this one first?
- Yes, that one's better.
- Either this or that.
- It's either this or that.
- Yes.
- This way, it's easy for these two, - Do you want me to do it?
- Yes, sure.
- I think.
- I'll go for it.
- Bring them to the center.
- Toward the center.
- Yes.
(The plan is to send them to as inward as possible.)
They will stick together.
(Goal achieved)
Okay.
Only two magnets are left.
It was better to go first.
- Why did we...
- Right?
(The farther magnet, the closer magnet)
- Please.
I'll pull it off with this one.
- Really?
- Okay.
That'll make it...
(He chose the farther magnet, which is harder.)
much easier for me.
(They stuck together!)
It's much easier for me.
I told you I'm good at it.
I already told you.
But it went the same way during the last spare time.
- We excelled in the 1st 2 rounds.
- That's right.
But we ended up winning in the last round.
That's how it goes.
- So...
- When we succeed so fast,
- I get nervous.
- I think they're onto something.
They're onto something.
- Round 3 will be super hard.
- Round 3 will make no sense.
- Go for it for now.
- For now...
- Go for it.
- It's better to finish it quickly.
- Don't make any mistakes.
- No.
Right. Don't try to be funny.
Don't try to be funny.
- Here.
- Okay!
Hey, guys!
- Yes!
- Okay!
(A perfect finish)
- Yes!
- Okay!
Hey, guys!
- Round Two, success!
- Success!
(Round 2 success!)
Now, we still have eight tries.
You have your blocks now. What now, Tae Oh?
Please talk to your friends about going further or stopping now.
- Go for it.
- Listen, though.
- Go.
- Round Three...
- might be really tough.
- I can be tough.
You might lose them all.
- Then, it's...
- Stop.
- I mean, we still have eight tries.
- Please think carefully.
- Keep talking.
- Share your thoughts.
We have eight tries.
- Stop.
- No, keep going.
- Go.
I think I've seen this shot during the World Cup.
It was when they were deciding who would take the penalty kick.
(A strategy session as serious as an international match)
Now, have you decided?
- Yes.
You won't change your minds, right?
No.
In 1, 2, 3...
- Go!
How can they shout it so loudly?
Okay. Let's go for it.
Let's take it to the end.
- It's big.
- I want to try it.
- It's so big.
- Please let it be Nintendo.
- Please.
- Isn't it just snacks?
Please let it be Nintendo.
Please let it be the game console.
- Please.
- Nintendo.
Nintendo!
"After appearing on the show, my next wish is..."
"to have a game console."
"Four Nintendo Switches."
(The presents for Round 3, 4 Nintendo Switches)
(Screaming)
(The game console that was in last night's dream)
- It's a festival here.
- Yes.
Gosh. Look at them.
They really brought them.
- Gosh.
- Four Nintendo game consoles.
- That's great.
- We have four of them.
- Yes.
- Look at the colors.
- They're so pretty!
- Come here.
- Come.
- It has nice colors.
What's going on?
- Hey.
- It's crazy.
Gosh. This is...
There are now game consoles.
(Round 3)
(The magnetic marble becomes smaller...)
(while there are more magnets to stick.)
(It's become much smaller.)
(There is one more magnet.)
- Gosh.
- There's an additional magnet?
(1 person should flick twice as there are 5 magnets to flick.)
- It's a bit hard.
- Well...
No, they can do it.
- They can do it.
- They have eight tries left.
- It's so small.
Gosh. It's really small.
But think of it as big as the last one.
(The target has shrunken compared to the last time.)
(They start practicing.)
- We might need the chance.
- We need to cheer loudly.
But Jae Seok...
- It might go out.
- Was that a practice?
- It might fall off.
- Gosh.
(He barely succeeds.)
It'll be difficult from now on.
(Because it's lighter, a light flick can move it farther.)
It's getting tougher now.
It might fall off.
Exactly.
It'll be tough from now on.
(He's a long-range specialist.)
Hold on.
You shouldn't send it all the way.
- It's possible. I told you.
- Nice.
- It might fall off now.
- It can't fall off.
- Flick it smoothly.
- This is just practice.
I'll pull it off right away because it's a practice.
(Laughing)
It was a practice.
- It was a practice. It's okay.
- It's okay.
It's okay to fail.
Let's try it.
- Shall we?
- Yes. Let's do it.
Just think nothing has changed.
- Yes.
- Don't feel pressured.
- Just relax.
- Let's get it.
- Yes!
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Yes!
It's for the game consoles.
Let's cheer up for the last time.
In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go!
- Let's go!
They're louder than anyone we've had.
- Yes.
- Who's going to flick first?
- What about Ki Joo this time?
- Ki Joo, go for it.
(Ki Joo goes first again.)
- She's brave.
- She does it well...
in a calm manner.
- That was good.
- Hey.
- Good job.
- That wasn't bad, was it?
- Yes. That was great.
- Yes.
It was better than not bad.
You did it much better than in practice.
- Then I should flick that way.
- Hold on, Jae Seok.
- I need to stick them over there.
- Right?
You have a 99 percent chance to succeed.
- Totally.
- Bring them together over here.
I'll go for it.
It's easy, Jae Seok.
- What was that?
- It's super easy.
What was that?
What?
- That was strange.
- It's okay.
- He made a strange trick.
- But still,
- you can go for it.
- We can stick the three together.
- You can send it here.
- Isn't that right?
- It's not over yet.
- No, it's not.
- It's not over.
- Gosh, Jae Seok.
- Seriously.
- It's not over.
- This magnet can go that way.
- Then...
- they will all stick together.
- Yes.
- It's not over yet.
- That's even better.
- That's right.
- I flick it into the gap.
Okay.
- Gosh.
- Tae Hyun.
(Emergency!)
It's fine.
- Hit this one.
- Right. Hit it.
Or...
- Move this in?
- Right.
- Hit it.
- I should push it like this.
- Start with the closer one.
- I'll hit it hard.
- Okay.
Don't hit it too hard. Use enough power.
You made it like this at the start.
Exactly.
The direction seems off.
(Peeking)
- Gosh, I feel so much pressure.
- They're going wild behind you.
- They want the Nintendo.
- They're going wild.
- Gosh, my hands are shaking.
- Come here.
- Hurry!
- It's okay.
- We have many tries left.
- Do whatever you want.
- Please!
We have many tries left.
It pushed it away?
- It pushed it away?
- It gets pushed away.
- The magnet...
- Why did it push it away?
Why didn't they stick together?
There are two poles of a magnet.
- They had it all planned.
- The two poles.
(The same poles of a magnet push each other away.)
Are they the same pole?
You should finish it up, Ki Joo.
- Clash them together.
- Go for it.
- After hitting the middle, - Clash them together.
send this here, and get them together.
I'll give it a try.
- Right.
- Ki Joo went earlier.
I'll try hitting it hard.
- Right.
- You should just hit it.
It might work.
- Why won't they stick?
- Hold on.
- Why won't they stick together?
- Check this out. Why is that?
(They start studying the magnets.)
- The sides are different.
- I see.
They're of different poles.
These stick together.
Gosh, it's a game of luck.
- So that's what we must consider.
- This one is the problem.
- Right.
- We must check the sides?
That's too hard to do.
- How do we check the sides?
- That's too hard to do.
Gosh.
Let's give it a try.
- We were lucky earlier.
- Right.
- We did it by luck.
- We were lucky earlier.
We'll make it within our tries, won't we?
Right.
All right. This is our fourth try.
Our 4th try of Round 3.
Let's do a cheer. One, two, three!
- Let's go!
- Here we go?
- Here we go.
You should start, Yeon Shik.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
It's just the first shot.
(Yeon Seok goes 1st.)
You can make it simple for the first shot.
- Right.
- Hit it lightly.
Comfortably. Lightly.
Lightly.
(Yeon Seok manages to pull off his shot.)
It went too far.
Go next, Ki Joo. It's a close shot.
You always make Ki Joo go when it's a hard one.
- Hey.
- Move it here.
Is it better for this one to be sent to the front?
- Or should I move it a lot?
- You can do that.
- I think it will fall.
- You can move it here...
or you can hit it to move it.
- For now...
- Nintendo!
Hey, kids. Are you not watching us play?
- I keep hearing "Nintendo."
- That's all they're focused on.
- So this is what it's like.
- They're doing their challenge.
Right.
Let's stay focused.
- You did it.
Hold on.
- It's hard to get the sides.
- If it gets hit from that side,
it will most likely fall apart.
These sides don't seem to stick.
It'll depend on our luck now.
These parts stick, but not the sides.
The direction is...
- You should move it to this side.
- Right.
- Okay!
- There we go.
- Gosh.
- We're almost there.
- I didn't go.
We're almost there.
What should I do? Should I hit this one?
Should I move this one or this one?
I think you should move this one.
- You should move this one first.
- Right.
- Leave it for the last one?
- Yes, for the last one.
Whether it works or not,
someone will have to give it a try.
- Go!
- Let's go!
Go!
All right.
Ki Joo is the decider.
Ki Joo!
- Let's go!
- She's the decider.
- Please!
- Round Three!
- If we pass Round Three,
you all will get the game device.
(One more magnet will earn them the game device.)
- Get ready.
- Hey!
(The game devices are right under their noses.)
(A big chance to break off an old jinx)
(Please!)
- Let's go!
- She's the decider.
- Please!
- Round Three!
- If we pass Round Three,
you all will get the game device.
(One more magnet will earn them the game device.)
(The game devices are right under their noses.)
(A big chance to break off an old jinx)
(Please!)
(Screaming)
(They finally break off the elementary school jinx.)
- Round Three, success!
- Success!
(They win the game devices.)
You've won it all.
(The first success of this season.)
(They win the backpacks, LEGO packs, and game devices.)
Gosh, this is awesome!
This is truly awesome!
- Are you happy?
- Yes!
- Gosh, Tae Oh.
- What a great day.
- Yes!
Not even Santa can give out this many gifts.
- Come this way.
- Not even Santa can do this.
- My hands are full.
- Right.
- Your hands are full! How great!
- You can carry them like this.
- Gosh, Ki Joo.
- Great.
- You were amazing.
- Gosh!
(Ki Joo's shot was crucial.)
- She would've felt nervous.
- It wasn't an easy shot.
- Ki Joo did a great job.
- This is unbelievable.
- We met these four children today.
- What a relief.
- We have...
- Finally!
finally gone past Round Three.
(Feeling proud)
We finally broke that curse.
He's Whenever Possible's...
- He's our gem.
- Right.
- It was amazing.
He comes every season to give us a great boost.
- Thank you once again.
- Gosh.
- I thank you even more.
- Right.
How well shall I continue to perform as a gem?
- You were amazing today.
- Can I be on a different show?
Should I come here only or should I go somewhere else?
- You should stick with us.
- Okay.
- Just be with us.
- Exclusive to this show.
- Ki Joo was crucial.
- Ki Joo did a great job.
- Right.
I feel so proud today.
I managed to win the Nintendo that was echoing in my ears.
I think I can sleep well today.
Thank you so much once again.
I would like to thank...
everyone who was on our show today.
- Thank you!
- Congratulations!
(What was it like being on Whenever Possible?)
It was really exciting,
and it will become a great memory.
Thank you for being on the show with me.
Whenever Possible!
- Thank you for playing well!
We have time.
(Hyun Bin)
(Your hands are shaking so much.)
(You did it! Take it out well.)
(Be quiet!)
Do you have any ties to Anyang?
I was born and raised here.
(Woo Do Hwan)
Go!
(This is an opportunity.)
I think I can do well.
(Destroy!)
(Destroy it!)
Let's go for it right away.
That was awesome!
(A thrilling game...)
(in Anyang)
Please!
Please call out, "Here I go."
Hold on.
(I hate that line so much.)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)